Register of the Mont Pèlerin Society records
Hoover Institution Archives
- 2011 INCREMENTAL MATERIALS, 1974-2005 (Boxes 65-138)
  - Edwin J. Feulner discussion paper, Vienna, 1996 (Box 116)
  - Proposed regional meeting, Cancun, Mexico, 1996 January 14-17 (Box 116)
  - Cancun conference materials, 1996 (Box 116)
  - Bradley Foundation Fellows, Cancun, 1996 (Box 116)
  - Earhart Foundation, Mexico, 1996 (Box 116)
  - Carthage Foundation, Mexico regional meeting, 1996 January 14-17 (Box 116)
  - Cancun, Mexico accounts, 1996 (Box 117)
  - Cancun regional meeting I, 1996 January 14-17 (Box 117)
  - Cancun regional meeting II, 1996 January 14-17 (Box 117)
  - Cancun regional meeting III, 1996 January 14-17 (Box 117)
  - Expenses, 1996 (Box 118)
  - Tax, 1996 (Box 118)
  - Accounting, 1996 (Box 118)
  - General, 1996, after Vienna, 1996 September (Box 118)
  - Expenses, 1996-1997 (Box 118)
  - Templeton prize, 1996 (Box 118)
  - Directory corrections, 1996 (Box 118)
  - John Templeton file, 1996 (Box 118)
  - Contributions, 1996-1997 (Box 118)
  - Fundraising letters, 1996 (Box 119)
  - Checks received, copies, 1996 (Box 119)
  - Sequoia checking account, 1996-1997 (Box 119)
  - National Capital Bank, 1996 (Box 119)
  - Sequoia Money Market account, 1996-1997 (Box 119)
  - New members nomination forms, 1996 (Box 119)
  - Edwin J. Feulner speeches, Barcelona, Mont Pèlerin, 1997 (Box 120)
  - Barcelona regional meeting, 1997 (Box 120)
  - Board meeting, Barcelona regional meeting, 1997 September 7 (Box 120)
  - Special gathering feedback, 1997 (Box 120)
  - Funding special gathering, 1997 (Box 120)
  - Papers/comments, Mont Pèlerin, 1997 (Box 120)
  - Miller tribute, 1997 (Box 120)
  - Hotel bill, Mont Pèlerin, 1997 (Box 120)
  - Attendees, Mont Pèlerin, 1997 (Box 120)
  - Program, Mont Pèlerin, 1997 (Box 120)
  - Handbook, Mont Pèlerin, 1997 (Box 121)
  - Correspondence I, Mont Pèlerin, 1997 (Box 121)
  - Correspondence II, Mont Pèlerin, 1997 (Box 121)
  - Checks received, 1997-1998 (Box 121)
  - Expenses, 1997 (Box 122)
  - General correspondence, 1997 (Box 122)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society article, Frankfurter Allgemiene, 1997 (Box 122)
  - National Capital Bank, 1997 (Box 122)
  - Sequoia money market account, 1997 (Box 122)
  - Sequoia checking account, 1997 (Box 122)
  - Annual dues, 1997-1998 (Box 122)
  - Expenses/contract, Washington DC meeting, 1998 (Box 123)
  - Hayek essay entries, circa 1997 (Box 123)
  - American host committee response, 1998 (Box 123)
  - Golden anniversary host committee letter, 1998 (Box 123)
  - Articles for golden anniversary meeting, 1998 (Box 123)
  - Papers, Washington DC, 1998 (Box 123)
  - Edwin J. Feulner remarks, golden anniversary meeting, 1998 (Box 123)
  - Earhart Fellows, 1998 (Box 123)
  - Dinners/receptions, 1997 (Box 123)
  - Scholarship applications, 1997 (Box 123)
  - Projected income budget, 1997 (Box 124)
  - Annual registration I, 1998-1999 (Box 124)
  - Annual registration II, 1998-1999 (Box 124)
  - Expenses, 1998 (Box 124)
  - Correspondence I, 1998 (Box 124)
  - Correspondence II, 1998 (Box 124)
  - Correspondence, 1998 November-December (Box 124)
  - Correspondence, 1998 September-October (Box 124)
  - Bill Campbell, Swiss Review, 1998 (Box 125)
  - Previous nomination forms I, 1998 (Box 125)
  - Previous nomination forms II, 1998 (Box 125)
  - Weekly updates, 1998 (Box 125)
  - Members papers I, 1998 (Box 125)
  - Members papers II, 1998 (Box 125)
  - Credit card receipts, 1998 (Box 125)
  - Handbook, circa 1998 (Box 126)
  - Golden anniversary solicitations, 1998 (Box 126)
  - Golden anniversary meeting reimbursements, 1998 (Box 126)
  - Registrations A-L, Washington DC, 1998 (Box 127)
  - Registrations M-Z, Washington DC, 1998 (Box 127)
  - Conference binders, golden anniversary meeting, Washington DC, 1998 (Box 128)
  - Potsdam meeting, 1999 (Box 129)
  - Santiago general meeting, 2000 (Box 129)
  - General meeting Santiago, Chile, conference material, 2000 (Box 129)
  - Conference binder, Bratislava, 2001 (Box 129)
  - Board meeting materials, Bratislava, 2001 (Box 129)
  - Bali meeting program and papers, 1999 July 8-11 (Box 130)
  - Bali meeting, 1999 (Box 130)
  - Vancouver meeting, 1999 (Box 130)
  - Vancouver, 1999 (Box 130)
  - Regional meeting conference materials, 1999 October 26-30 (Box 130)
  - Membership dues A-L, 2000-2001 (Box 131)
  - Membership dues M-Z, 2000-2001 (Box 131)
  - Membership dues A-L, 2001-2002 (Box 131)
  - Membership dues M-Z, 2001-2002 (Box 132)
  - Membership dues A-L, 2002-2003 (Box 132)
  - Membership dues M-Z, 2002-2003 (Box 132)
  - Membership dues A-L, 2003-2004 (Box 133)
  - Membership dues M-Z, 2003-2004 (Box 133)
  - Membership dues A-L, 2004-2005 (Box 134)
  - Membership dues M-Z, 2004-2005 (Box 134)
  - Garvey essay, 1992 (Box 135)
  - Garvey essay submissions, 1992 (Box 135)
  - Garvey essay ads, etcetera, circa 1990 (Box 135)
  - Garvey notices to send, 1990 (Box 135)
  - Garvey essay correspondence, 1992 (Box 135)
  - Garvey essay ads, 1992 (Box 135)
  - Garvey essay contest general, 1991 (Box 135)
  - Garvey essay judges information, 1992 (Box 135)
  - Garvey Fellowships correspondence (Box 136)
  - Olive W. Garvey Fellowship expenses (Box 136)
  - Garvey essay contest, 1982 (Box 136)
  - Garvey essay, 1982 (Box 136)
  - Olive W. Garvey contest, 1984 (Box 136)
  - Olive Garvey ads, 1984 (Box 137)
  - Garvey essays, final copies, 1984 (Box 137)
  - Garvey essays to proofread, 1984 (Box 137)
  - Aequus Institute, general (Box 137)
  - Photo annotated by Gloria Valentine, Milton Friedman's assistant, undated (Box 138)
- 2013 INCREMENTAL MATERIALS, 1976-2012 (Boxes 138-164)
  - By-Laws, 2008 (Box-folder 139: 1)
  - 2012 (Box-folder 139: 2-3)
  - Special regional meeting, 2004 (Box-folder 139: 4)
  - Buenos Aires papers, 2011 (Box-folder 139: 5-6)
  - Board minutes, Vancouver, 1999 (Box-folder 139: 7)
  - "Challenges to Liberalism in the 21st Century,", 2006 (Box-folder 140: 1)
    Includes one CD with presentation papers on the meeting topic "Challenges to Liberalism in the 21st Century."
  - Regional meeting, "The Populist Challenge to Latin American Society,", 2011 (Box-folder 140: 2)
  - Newspaper clipping, 1997 (Box-folder 140: 3)
    Samtag, 29. Marz 1997, Nr. 74/ Seite 15
  - "A History of the Mont Pèlerin Society," by R. M. Hartwel, 1995 (Box-folder 140: 4)
  - Conference planning material, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 140: 5)
  - Copy of proceedings of the 1947 Mont Pèlerin Conference, 1997 (Box-folder 140: 6)
  - Copy of proceedings of the 1947 Mont Pèlerin Conference, 1997 (Box-folder 140: 7)
  - F. A. Hayek essay competition, 1994 (Box-folder 141: 1)
  - Essay materials, 1976-1987 (Box-folder 141: 2)
  - General meeting, Cannes, 1994 (Box-folder 141: 3-5)
  - Board member memos, 1997 (Box-folder 141: 6)
  - The Olive W. Garvey essay competition, winning and honorable mention essays, 1984 (Box-folder 142: 1)
  - Special meeting, speakers' papers, 2011 (Box-folder 142: 2)
  - Reform Review, 2007-2010 (Box-folder 142: 3)
  - Notes on economic theories, 1966 (Box-folder 142: 4)
  - Accounting documentation, 1999 (Box-folder 142: 5)
  - Regional meeting list of participants, 2005 (Box-folder 142: 6)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1997-2006 (Box-folder 142: 7)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1988-2008 (Box-folder 142: 8)
  - Board meeting minutes, 1988-2009 (Box-folder 143: 1)
  - Papers presented at the special gathering 50th anniversary, 1997 (Box-folder 143: 2)
    Includes six photographs.
  - Draft materials for 50th anniversary publication (Box-folder 143: 3)
  - General meeting, "Europe in an Open World Order" conference papers, 1990 (Box-folder 143: 4)
  - General meeting conference paper drafts, 1990 (Box-folder 143: 5)
  - Essays honoring Friedrich A. Hayek (Box-folder 143: 6)
  - Essays, 1975-1987 (Box-folder 144: 1)
  - Financial file general meeting/ Washington, D.C., 1998 (Box-folder 144: 2)
  - Materials from general meeting, invoices, bills, and meeting minutes, 1998 (Box-folder 144: 3)
  - Meeting, 2008 (Box-folder 144: 4)
    Meeting in Tokyo, Japan, with topic "Technology and Freedom."
  - Life members, 2002-2008 (Box-folder 144: 5)
    Correspondence notifying members of lifetime membership status.
  - Website, 1999 (Box-folder 144: 6)
  - Correspondence, 2003 (Box-folder 144: 7)
  - London 2002 correspondence, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 145: 1)
  - Chattanooga 2003, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 145: 2)
  - Correspondence, 1999 January-May (Box-folder 145: 3)
  - Correspondence, 2002 October 5 (Box-folder 145: 4)
  - Correspondence, 2002 October 7 (Box-folder 145: 5)
  - Correspondence, 2002 October 8 (Box-folder 145: 6)
  - Correspondence, 2002 October 9 (Box-folder 145: 7)
  - Correspondence, London, to take, 2002 (Box-folder 145: 8)
  - Correspondence, 2002 (Box-folder 145: 9)
  - Correspondence, 2003 (Box-folder 145: 10)
  - London grants, 2002 (Box-folder 146: 1)
    Correspondence and documentation regarding funding for the 2002 Mont Pèlerin Society general meeting.
  - Fellowship requests correspondence, 2002 (Box-folder 146: 2)
  - Correspondence and registration updates regarding 2002 meeting (Box-folder 146: 3)
  - London new members, 2002 (Box-folder 146: 4)
  - Correspondence, 2002 Roe Grants, London (Box-folder 146: 5)
  - Annual general meeting, 2002 October 9 (Box-folder 146: 6)
    Notes and correspondence regarding 2002 general meeting.
  - Correspondence, 1999 June (Box-folder 146: 7)
  - Chattanooga grants, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 146: 8)
  - Nomination correspondence, 2003 (Box-folder 146: 9)
  - Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 146: 10)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 146: 11)
  - "Intellectual Pilgrims: The Fiftieth Anniversary of the Mont Pèlerin Society," authored by Edwin J. Feulner, 1999 (Box-folder 147: 1)
  - Guestbook from 1998 golden anniversary of the Mont Pèlerin Society (Box-folder 147: 2)
  - Correspondence, 1999 (Box-folder 147: 3)
  - Hayek essay, 2006 (Box-folder 147: 4)
  - Contributions, 2004 (Box-folder 147: 5)
  - Winter newsletter draft, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 147: 6)
  - Dues, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 147: 7)
    Correspondence regarding member dues.
  - Hamburg, 2004 (Box-folder 147: 8)
    Correspondence regarding 2004 Hamburg Mont Pèlerin Society meeting.
  - Board meeting action items, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 147: 9)
  - Guest nominations - Hamburg 2004 correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 147: 10)
  - Life members correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 147: 11)
  - William E. Simon prize program Advisory Board conference call, 2005 (Box-folder 148: 1-3)
  - National Capital Bank statements, 2000 (Box-folder 148: 4)
  - Sequoia checking account statements, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 148: 5)
  - Acorn International, investment bank statements, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 148: 6)
  - Tax, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 149: 1)
    Materials concerning finances and audit.
  - Lindner Funds financial information, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 149: 2)
  - "Mount Vernon Statement" newspaper clippings, 2010 (Box-folder 149: 3)
  - Audit for the year, March 31, 1999, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 149: 4)
    Financial information, including 1998 990 tax form, invoices, correspondence, and itemized financial report.
  - Tax return, 1998 (Box-folder 149: 5)
  - 1997 tax return, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 149: 6)
    Includes 1996 and 1997 tax forms.
  - 1099 forms for the 1999 tax year (Box-folder 149: 7)
  - Tax forms - 1099 for 1998 (Box-folder 149: 8)
  - Taxes, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 150: 1)
    Includes 1996 tax form.
  - Tax, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 150: 2)
  - Sequoia money market account financial information, 1998 (Box-folder 150: 3)
  - U.S. Gold transaction summary statements from United Services Fund, 1988-1996 (Box-folder 150: 4)
  - Financial information, 1997 990 tax form, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 150: 5)
  - Sequoia checking account 1998, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 150: 6)
  - Expenses, 1999 (Box-folder 150: 7)
  - Taxes, fiscal year 1999 (Box-folder 150: 8)
  - National Capital Bank, 1999 (Box-folder 150: 9)
  - Sequoia National Bank, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 150: 10)
  - Bills (Mondays), 1999-2000 (Box-folder 150: 11)
  - Audit, 1999 (Box-folder 150: 12)
    Includes 1999 990 tax form.
  - Papers presented at the golden anniversary meeting, 1998 (Box-folder 151: 1-2)
  - Weekly reports, 2005 (Box-folder 151: 3)
  - General meeting, Sydney, 2010 (Box-folder 151: 4-5)
  - Conference materials, Washington, D.C. 50th anniversary meeting, "Free Markets and Free People - The Barriers Remaining,", 1998 (Box-folder 151: 6-7)
  - Hayek essay entries, Spanish responses, 2006 (Box-folder 152: 2)
  - Brandywine Funds financial information, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 152: 3)
  - Brandywine Funds, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 152: 4)
  - Hussman Funds statements and records, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 152: 5)
  - Deposits, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 152: 6)
  - Audit, 2005 (Box-folder 152: 7)
  - 1099 tax forms, 2006 (Box-folder 152: 8)
  - National Capital Bank, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 152: 9)
  - United Bank C.D. records, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 152: 10)
  - United Bank money market account, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 152: 11)
  - United Bank statements and records, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 152: 12)
  - Audit, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 152: 13)
  - Longleaf Partner's Fund, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 152: 14)
  - Longleaf Partner's Funds records, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 152: 15)
  - Hennessy Funds statements/records, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 152: 16)
  - Colombia Management Acorn International Funds records, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 152: 17)
  - Audit, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 152: 18)
    Includes 2003 990 tax form.
  - United Bank deposits/transfers, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 153: 1)
  - United Bank, 2004 (Box-folder 153: 2)
  - United Bank checking account, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 153: 3)
  - United Bank money market account, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 153: 4)
  - Salt Lake City grants, 2004 (Box-folder 153: 5)
  - Liberty/Acorn, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 153: 6)
  - Checks, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 153: 7)
  - United Bank wire information, 2004 (Box-folder 153: 8)
  - Tax related, 2003 (Box-folder 153: 9)
    Tax form 8868, "Application for Extension of Time to File an Exempt Organization Return."
  - Lindner Funds, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 153: 10)
  - Audit, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 153: 11)
  - Sequoia checking account, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 153: 12)
  - National Capital Bank, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 153: 13)
  - 2005 audit, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 153: 14)
    Includes 2004 990 tax form.
  - Checks, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 154: 1)
  - Sequoia Bank, 2003 (Box-folder 154: 2)
  - Auditor: Aukamp, 2004 (Box-folder 154: 3)
  - 2004 tax related, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 154: 4)
  - Hussman Strategic Growth, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 154: 5)
  - Longleaf Partner's Funds, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 154: 6)
  - Lindner/ Hennessy, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 154: 7)
  - 3 month C.D., 2003-2004 (Box-folder 154: 8)
  - Liberty/Acorn, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 154: 9)
  - Brandywine Funds, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 154: 10)
  - National Capital Bank, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 154: 11)
  - United Bank/Sequoia deposits/transfers, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 154: 12)
  - Sequoia checking, 2001 (Box-folder 154: 13)
  - National Capital Bank, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 154: 14)
  - Sequoia money market, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 154: 15)
  - Longleaf Partners, 2002 (Box-folder 154: 16)
  - Lindner Funds, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 154: 17)
  - Liberty/Acorn, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 154: 18)
  - Sequoia money market account, 2001 (Box-folder 154: 19)
  - Audit, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 154: 20)
    Includes 2001 990 tax form.
  - Brandywine Funds, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 154: 21)
  - Sequoia Bank checking account, 2001 (Box-folder 154: 22)
  - Audit materials, 2001 (Box-folder 155: 1-2)
    Includes 1 floppy disk.
  - National Capital Bank, 2001 (Box-folder 155: 3)
  - Longleaf Partners Fund, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 155: 4)
  - Audit materials, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 155: 5)
  - Longleaf Partners Fund, 2002 (Box-folder 155: 6)
  - Lindner Funds, 2002 (Box-folder 155: 7)
  - Liberty/Acorn, 2002 (Box-folder 155: 8)
  - National Capital Bank, 2002 (Box-folder 155: 9)
  - Brandywine Funds, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 155: 10)
  - Sequoia money market, 2002 (Box-folder 155: 11)
  - Sequoia checking account, 2002 (Box-folder 155: 12)
  - Tax related (for 990), 2002 (Box-folder 155: 13)
    Includes 2002 990 tax form.
  - 25 year celebration, 2002 (Box-folder 155: 14)
  - Invoices and bills, 2003 (Box-folder 155: 15)
  - Checks, invoices and bills, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 156: 1)
  - Transfers/deposits, money market account, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 156: 2)
  - Audit, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 156: 3)
  - Deposits, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 156: 4)
  - Checks and payments for expense reports, bills, invoices, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 156: 5)
  - "Private Savings and the Provision of Social Security in Japan," essay authored by Kenji Komatsu, 1980 (Box-folder 156: 6)
  - "Liberalism and Compromise in the U.S. Congress," essay authored by Edwin J Feulner and Robert L. Schuettinger, 1976 (Box-folder 156: 7)
  - Materials from Mont Pèlerin Society visit to the Chung-Hua Institution for Economic Research, 1988 (Box-folder 156: 8)
  - Regional meeting, Big Sky, Montana, United States, 1991 (Box-folder 156: 9-11)
  - General meeting papers, Hoover Institution, Stanford, California, 1980 (Box-folder 157: 1)
  - Regional meeting papers, Stockholm, Sweden, 1981 (Box-folder 157: 2)
  - Regional meeting papers, Guatemala, 1990 (Box-folder 157: 3)
  - Special meeting papers, Taipei, China, 1988 (Box-folder 157: 4)
  - Regional meeting papers, Christchurch, New Zealand, 1989 (Box-folder 157: 5-6)
  - Regional meeting papers, Sydney, Australia, 1985 (Box-folder 158: 1-2)
  - Goa, correspondence, speaker's papers, 2002 (Box-folder 158: 3)
  - Santiago 2000, financial, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 158: 4)
  - Santiago 2000 correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 158: 5)
  - 1999 new member acceptance letters, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 158: 6)
  - Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 158: 7)
  - Goa finances, correspondence regarding 2002 meeting in Goa, India (Box-folder 158: 8)
  - 1999 regional meeting information and correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 158: 9)
  - List of attendees, correspondence and notes, 2002 (Box-folder 159: 1)
  - Santiago correspondence, 2000 (Box-folder 159: 2)
  - Santiago 2000 new members, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 159: 3)
  - Santiago Board meetings, 2000 (Box-folder 159: 4)
  - 2000 general meeting proposals, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 159: 5)
  - Bratislava 2000, correspondence, 2001 (Box-folder 159: 6)
  - Regional meeting Hamburg, conference materials, 2004 (Box-folder 159: 7)
  - Member updated address, 2004 (Box-folder 160: 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 2003 (Box-folder 160: 2)
    Email forwarding an article written by Ronald Hamowy regarding Murray N. Rothbard and F. A. Hayek.
  - Membership nominations, 2002 (Box-folder 160: 3)
  - Presidential addresses, 1988-1997 (Box-folder 160: 4)
  - Correspondence, 2000 (Box-folder 160: 5)
  - General email correspondence, 2004 (Box-folder 160: 6)
  - Reflections on Mont Pèlerin Society, 1951-1997 (Box-folder 160: 7)
  - Board action items, 1996-2006 (Box-folder 160: 8)
  - Hayek essay entries 1-29, 2006 (Box-folder 161: 1)
  - Hayek essay entries 30-46, 2006 (Box-folder 161: 2)
  - Hayek essay entries 47-66, 2006 (Box-folder 161: 3)
  - 1998 Hayek essay contest, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 161: 4)
    Includes 1996 winning essays.
  - Hayek essay, 2002 (Box-folder 161: 5)
    Includes correspondence about advertising in The Weekly Standard.
  - Hayek essay winners, 2002 (Box-folder 161: 6)
    Includes one letter of acceptance.
  - Corporate press, 2002 (Box-folder 161: 7)
  - Hayek essay contest, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 161: 8)
    Includes 1 mini CD-R.
  - Correspondence regarding Carlos Menem, 1992 (Box-folder 162: 1)
  - Future newsletter information, 1999 (Box-folder 162: 2)
    Includes errata from 1999 membership directory.
  - Draft of newsletter, 2004 (Box-folder 162: 3)
  - Newspaper articles, 1997 (Box-folder 162: 4)
  - Hoover files, 2002 (Box-folder 162: 5)
    Finding aid for Mont Pèlerin Society records
  - Mont Pèlerin Society Newsletter, 2002 Summer (Box-folder 162: 6)
    Notes, drafts, correspondence, and newspaper clippings
  - Mont Pèlerin Society Newsletter, 2003 Spring (Box-folder 162: 7)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society Newsletter, 1995-2004 (Box-folder 162: 8)
  - 2004 Hayek essay contest, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 162: 9)
    Articles, essay drafts, and correspondence
  - Mont Pèlerin Society 50th remarks, 1998 (Box-folder 162: 10)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society Newsletter, 51.1, 1999 (Box-folder 162: 11)
    Drafts and correspondence
  - Mont Pèlerin Society Newsletter, 50.1, 1998 February (Box-folder 162: 12)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society Newsletter, 49.2, 1997 July (Box-folder 162: 13)
  - Correspondence regarding newsletter, 1996 (Box-folder 162: 14)
    Correspondence and drafts of articles
  - Mont Pèlerin Society Newsletter, 49.1, 1997 March (Box-folder 162: 15)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society Newsletter, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 162: 16)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society Newsletter, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 163: 1)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society Newsletter, 1989-1999 (Box-folder 163: 2)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society Newsletter, 2000-2011 (Box-folder 163: 3)
  - Hayek essay contest flyers, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 163: 4)
  - Correspondence, 1986-2001 (Box-folder 163: 5)
  - Correspondence, 1986-2001 (Box-folder 163: 6)
  - General meeting, Sydney, Australia, programme and participant list, 2010 (Box-folder 164: 1)
  - Hayek essay contest, Spanish entries, 2006 (Box-folder 164: 2)
  - N. Goto essay prize competition, winning essays, 1982 (Box-folder 164: 3)
  - "Industrial Policy: A Critique," authored by W. Duncan Reekie, paper delivered at the 1995 regional meeting, Cape Town, South Africa (Box-folder 164: 4)
  - Papers presented at the special meeting, Arlington, Virginia, 1994 (Box-folder 164: 5)
  - Photos from regional meeting in Cancun, Mexico, 1996 (Box-folder 164: 6)
    Includes 15 photographs.
  - Planning documentation from 1998 golden anniversary meeting in Washington, D.C. (Box-folder 164: 7)
  - Papers presented at the regional meeting in Cape Town, South Africa, 1995 (Box-folder 164: 8)
  - W. H. Hutt: An Economist for the Long Run, book with forward by Edwin J. Feulner, 1986 (Box-folder 164: 9)
  - F.A. Hayek essay competition, winning essays, 1996 (Box-folder 164: 10)
  - Membership directories, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 165: 1)
  - Membership directories, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 165: 2)
  - Membership directories, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 165: 3)
  - Membership directories, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 165: 4)
  - Membership directories, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 165: 5)
  - Membership directories, 2009-2011 (Box-folder 166: 1)
  - National Capital Bank, 1998 (Box-folder 166: 2)
  - Thank you letters, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 166: 3)